♪ Dan dan dan ♪
[Back in Time:
From Me to You]
It's for an audition
for the main lead
The main lead?
Me?
Their lead actor
suddenly left
so they're urgently
looking for a new one
It's just a replacement
but still, it's a great
opportunity for us
Of course it is!
I'm gonna
give my all to this
Do you know
Choi Hyobum?
He's a formal member in
Shin Yoo-il's idol group
He'll be your opposite
in this drama
[Back in Time:
From Me to You]
[Audition script]
Gosh, I'm nervous
No, relax, Hyesung
This is an opportunity
I've never dreamed of
I should be grateful
[Shindecent]
Hello?
What took you so long?
I don't wanna work
on my day off
Why are you so cold
all of a sudden?
Hang up if you have
nothing to say
You're auditioning
for a drama, right?
How did you know that?
I'll help you today
I'm off today
No thanks
I don't need your help
What the heck…
Help me? With what?